- [wind blowing]
- [suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues]
- [blender whirring]
- [chiming]
[gulping]
[sighs contentedly]
No wonder the January report was so late.
Unbelievable.
A 17-year-old wolf
with a whole life ahead of him
eats the leg of his friend, a deer.
How many more of these cases
do I have to see?
Oh, hang on.
REPORT
NAME: LEGOSHI
"The objective, which was mutually
agreed upon with the victim,
was to bring a devourer to justice"?
Really?
So we're fighting fire with fire,
are we, boys?
DISCHARGED
Interesting.
But still despicable.
TOP SECRET
He may have agreed to it,
but I sure as hell do not.
As the Beastar of this world,
I can't let it go.
AN ITCHY COLLAR
[suspenseful music playing]
[Legoshi groaning in agony]
BEAST APARTMENTS
[Legoshi groaning, whimpering]
- [Legoshi groaning, whimpering]
- [objects clattering]
[Legoshi continues groaning]
- [Legoshi groaning, panting]
- [objects thudding]
[Legoshi shouts]
[Legoshi groaning, whimpering]
[grunts]
[panting, straining]
- [Louis] I want you to eat me.
- [gasps]
[Legoshi] I swore
I'd never eat meat again.
I made a vow.
- [Saiga] Choose your favorite finger.
- [Legoshi] But the taste...
The texture.
- [Bill] Do you want a bite? Rabbit blood.
- [Legoshi] The flavor...
The moisture.
[pants, grunts]
So warm.
I'm powerless,
and sorrowful...
[Black Legoshi] You feel joy
from the bottom of your heart.
[Gohin] No matter how much
you struggle against it,
your true nature is that of
a brutal, vicious carnivore.
[Legoshi] I was always...
struggling with my own blood.
I want to make sure this world is a place
where Haru can live in peace.
[gasps softly]
And yet...
[growls softly]
...the blood that flows through these veins...
still wants for living flesh!
[screaming in agony]
[whimpers]
[groaning in agony]
[Seven sighs in annoyance]
- [Legoshi continues groaning]
- [Seven sighs]
Ugh! So loud!
Every night, it's the same thing!
And I have work in the morning!
[Legoshi continues groaning]
[Seven] What kind of person
acts like this?
Not even a "Hello, neighbor"
when he moved in.
Well, I got something to say to him!
[gasps]
- A wolf...
- [Legoshi grunts softly]
[Seven] What do I say?
Complaining might not be
the best way to start.
- [water flowing]
- [Seven sighs]
[Legoshi panting]
Uh, excuse me, sir?
- Huh?
- [exclaims]
Good evening. I'm Seven,
and I live in the room next door.
- It's a pleasure--
- [Legoshi gasps]
- [Seven gasps]
- [Legoshi exhales]
What's with him?
That's a rather rude way to treat people.
Unbelievable!
[Legoshi] Sorry about that, neighbor.
[train chugging]
[female dog grunting in distance]
[grunting, straining]
[Gohin] Hmm? No meat response.
[inhales deeply] If that dog really
isn't eating meat,
then these symptoms are a bit unusual.
If it's not meat intoxication...
[knock on door]
[Legoshi] It's me, I have your food!
Finally!
Come on in, kid.
Put it anywhere.
[Legoshi grunts softly]
[Legoshi] Straight-from-the-pot udon
with bamboo leaf topping.
Sorry for the wait. That's 500.
Nice uniform there.
You can pull off anything.
[scoffs] At least I'm not
dressing like a girl again.
Good. 'Cause I almost had a heart attack.
I thought my ex-wife had come back.
[laughs]
Well, sit down.
[gasps] What in the world are you doing?
[chuckles nervously] No, I'd rather stand.
- [female dog, faintly] Just one gulp.
- [Gohin slurping]
[female dog, straining] Kines...
So, uh, even though I had permission
to eat his leg, the truth is,
I was prepared
to make up for it in prison.
But then, thanks to Louis and the others
testifying for me...
[Gohin slurping]
...they ended up letting me go
with just a minor offense charge.
Although, "Record of prior devouring"
will have to stay in my file.
[Gohin] A scarred-up violent,
criminal virgin, huh? [scoffs]
So, you're still catching meat eaters
to bring 'em back here and treat 'em,
I take it?
[Gohin] Hmm.
Yeah, the situation's worse than ever.
I don't suppose you'd want to help me
with my work again, would you?
- [chuckles nervously]
- I can pay more than that udon place.
Forget it, I don't want to.
The whole thing's way too shady for me.
- What was that, you little punk?
- [Legoshi exclaims]
Look, I just mean, I want legitimate work,
out in the open.
I want to be a normal member of society
and lead a happy family life with Haru.
[gulps, sighs]
- And how's that family life going?
- Huh?
Uh, my family? I don't know--
Look, don't answer if you don't want to.
I was just curious is all.
[hesitates] Well...
I don't have a mom or dad.
I used to live with my grandpa.
[Gohin] Is your grandpa well?
[Legoshi] You know, probably...
[Gohin] Hmm. I see.
[Legoshi] We, uh...
We get along just fine and all,
but, I, uh... I haven't...
mentioned to him that I got arrested yet.
[Gohin sighs softly]
- Hang on a sec.
- Hmm?
- [Gohin] Here's the drugs.
- Oh, right.
[Gohin] Meat withdrawal symptoms
can be pretty severe
for up to three months or so.
- Better take them.
- [sighs] Yeah.
I appreciate it.
[Gohin] Sure.
- See you later.
- Yeah. All right, then.
[door bangs]
Ah!
- Legoshi!
- Uh, yeah?
"Record of prior devouring,"
was the official wording?
Yes.
Then I should say,
there's one thing you won't be able to do
with that in your file.
[Legoshi] Hmm?
Interspecies marriage with an herbivore.
What? I can't get married?
No!
Haru!
[objects clattering]
Oh, to be young and in love!
[Legoshi groaning softly]
[soft clattering]
[Louis sighs] Ibuki.
The king of the beasts
is supposed to be fierce and strong...
[chuckles softly]
...yet your rule was much like your mane.
Beautiful and gentle.
[gloomy guitar music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
How is it? The new leg, I mean.
It was remarkably easy
to learn to walk again.
[grunts softly]
You're quite fortunate.
It was built with the latest technology.
I only hope it won't affect your studies.
[grunts softly] No, sir. Thank you.
You do realize those legs of yours
are meant to walk the path of the heir
to The Horns Conglomerate.
They are not meant to feed
your carnivore friends.
Yes, sir.
I don't mind a little improvising,
but that's too far.
You're saying I should live
according to your script?
[Ogma chuckles] In a way.
But more importantly,
I want you to think for yourself,
find and fulfill your own role.
[Louis sighs]
[Louis] I thought that living
on the edges of society was the answer,
but I suppose now,
I have to confront
how I'm meant to live within it.
[upbeat music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
So I heard you went to the Black Market.
You lose your meat virginity yet?
- [chuckles]
- What kind did you get?
It was... I think, pig.
What, you "think"?
What do you mean, you "think"?
- Who cares what it was? I ate it.
- [student, sarcastically] Oh, yeah.
A year ago, that conversation
never would have happened.
- [Gon clears throat]
- [Jack] Hmm.
CHERRYTON OPENING CEREMONY
Welcome, all.
As you already know,
beginning with this academic year,
our carnivore and herbivore students
will be split into two separate
academic tracks.
You understand that we must, at all cost,
avoid a repeat of last year's tragedy.
I'm sure this may seem confusing,
but as Cherryton... [continues indistinctly]
[student 1] Maybe the classrooms
will smell better now.
[student 2] Getting rid of the dogs alone
will be enough.
[student 3] It'll be nice
to walk the hallways in peace.
[student 4] Frankly,
separate education is a relief.
Well, that's more weight
off our shoulders.
- [indistinct chatter]
- I guess so.
[Gon] As our last order of business,
I would like to announce the students
for this year's Advanced Class.
[student 1] Gonna the canines again.
- [student 2] For sure.
- Please stand up if your name is called.
Class A. Lando.
Class C. Danny.
Class E. Jack.
[all] Oh!
- [Gon] Class F. Lance.
- Whoo-hoo!
[Gon] And Class G. Mick.
That concludes our presentation.
[popping]
[all] Congratulations, Jack!
[chuckles softly] Thanks, you guys.
Our little boy is growing up so fast!
Legoshi's tail is going to go berserk
when he finds out.
[all laughing]
- [cell phone buzzing]
- Ah. Excuse me a second.
Hmm?
This is Jack.
[Gosha over phone] Ah, Jack!
Do you know where Legoshi is?
Who is-- Oh, is this
Legoshi's grandfather?
- Hey, sir, it's been ages!
- Legoshi's grandfather?
[Gosha] Is it true that Legoshi
dropped out of school?
His tuition was refunded, and, well...
I can't seem to get him
on the phone, either.
Do you know anything about this?
I know he canceled his phone service,
but I thought he'd already told you
he dropped out.
GRADUATION
[Gosha sighs] Sorry to get all worked up.
I'm just worried about him.
[Jack] Sir, please don't worry.
Legoshi knows what he's doing.
[Gosha] Yeah, but--
[Jack] I'm sure he had a good reason
for dropping out.
He wouldn't have done it
if it wasn't right for him.
He's the kind of guy you can trust.
[Gosha] I know. But after all,
the kid is my one and only grandchild.
[Lisa panting]
[Lisa] Ah, Haru! Hi!
[Haru] Hey! Come, sit.
[Lisa] Sorry we're late.
Orientation for the new students
dragged on forever.
- This is so great!
- Yeah.
- I'd been wanting to check this place out.
- They make an incredible latte here.
- That's exactly what I ordered.
- Really?
I have to get one next time.
- How was your course registration?
- Meh, I just chose whatever.
My first year of university is off
to such a fantastic start.
I've decided I want to make campus life
very exciting.
It's the perfect way to say goodbye
to the bullied high-school-kid life.
Hey, girls, guess what?
I wanted you to meet my new boyfriend,
so I invited him to join us.
- What?
- Huh?
You seriously got yourself
a man already? No way!
- Haru, did you know?
- Huh? Oh. No.
- So, what's he like?
- [Ako gasps] Here he comes now.
Wait-- Babe, over here!
- [both gasp]
- [heavy footsteps approaching]
[Lisa] Oh.
[grunts] Hey, ladies. The name's Eado, yo.
Ta-da! Meet my new baby boy.
[both gasping]
[Ako laughs]
That's pretty much
exactly how I thought you'd react.
Bit of a shock, huh?
Yeah, going out with Ako, we tend
to get that a lot around here. [chuckles]
- [Ako] Mmm-hmm.
- [sheep scoffs] Do you smell that?
- [sheep 2] Smells like a carnivore.
- [Lisa] Wow, that's great!
It's enough to make you lose
your appetite.
Can you even imagine
a boyfriend from another species
back when we were in school?
They'd call you a sicko for that.
And, actually, they'd be right.
Staying with your own kind
is so much safer.
I just hope she figures that out.
Come on, let's get out of here.
[sheep 2 sighs] Good idea.
[sighs] And we were having
such a good time just now.
[sheep 1 sighs] What a shame.
- [Eado sighs]
- [sheep 2] Where to?
- [sheep 1] Uh, anywhere?
- [sheep 2] Like...
[Ako, Eado sigh]
[Haru] Oh, Legoshi,
turns out the real world is
a lot more complicated than I thought.
COEXISTENCE THEORY: THE BASICS
VEGETABLE NUTRITION
[horn sounding]
[rhythmic drumming]
[festive music playing]
[muffled playing continues]
Young folks probably don't even know,
but way back when,
we had all sorts of events like this
that we'd be excited for.
I still remember it all
like it was yesterday.
Originally, this was a day that we had
to celebrate precious meat, to cherish it.
That's why it's called Meat-Loving Day.
And now, it's nothing but a day
to kick off turf wars
across the Black Market.
Between the Komodo dragons' Doku-Gumi...
[muffled whooping, cheering]
[Saiga] ...the red foxes' Inari-Gumi,
the leopards' Madara-Gumi,
and the lions' Shishi-Gumi.
[whooping, cheering continue]
[Saiga] That gang was thriving beautifully
until last year,
but they've been slipping lately.
They don't have a boss now.
And you can't call yourself
a gang without one.
Anyway, it's Meat-Loving Day,
so I'm slashing prices.
If it's possible,
do try to only take one bite.
[sniffs]
Hang on, you're not a carnivore, are you--
[grunts, groans]
[ominous music playing]
[Legoshi retching]
- [Legoshi groaning, whimpering]
- [thudding, rumbling]
[groans in frustration] That's enough!
I'm going to deal with this
once and for all.
[Legoshi continues groaning]
[knocks on door]
- [Legoshi coughing]
- [opens door]
Huh? Well, that's not very safe.
- [door creaking]
- [Legoshi breathing heavily]
[suspenseful music playing]
[heavy breathing continues]
[low growling]
Excuse me...
Are you okay?
[yelping]
- [growls]
- [shuddering]
[growling]
[grinding]
[Agata] Seriously? You can't give us
even a little more time?
'Fraid not. You know full well
what the deal is.
If you don't bring the ingredients,
I can't make the drugs.
But we've been super busy lately.
We don't have time for that.
Busy doing what?
Eating your pretty boy boss?
- What?
- [both growl]
You realize this is your problem
more than ours?
You cats aren't the be-all-end-all
of the Hyperdrug.
I'm sure another gang would take the work.
What if we can figure out something
by next week, huh?
[scoffs] Talk about unreliable!
If you can't even come up
with a single piece of ivory,
that doesn't bode well
for our relationship.
- [Melon sighs]
- [thuds]
- Oh?
- [Melon] Sorry for the wait. How's this?
Oh. [chuckles excitedly]
The renowned Shishi-Gumi
comes through again!
Such gorgeous high-quality ivory!
Yo, who is that?
I don't know.
[Melon] I take it
you can make the drug now? Right?
- Don't miss the deadline.
- Uh, yes, sir!
Don't boss us around.
You're the ones
who almost missed the delivery.
[Melon inhales, sighs heavily]
[puffing playfully]
Uh...
[nervously] Uh... Uh...
- [whimpers]
- [Melon sighs, grunts]
Punk! What do you think
you're doing-- [groans]
[Melon sighs] Silly cat,
let's get this straight.
[Dolph, Agata gasp]
[Melon] That's really no way
to talk to your boss...
- Now is it?
- [Free groans softly]
[closing theme song playing]
♪ Just like a new melody ♪
♪ Keep it beating on and on ♪
♪ I don't want to live without it ♪
♪ You give me the strength inside ♪
♪ Some things aren't meant to be ♪
♪ You say it like you know ♪
♪ But I really want you ♪
♪ I want you to see it the way I do ♪
♪ 'Cause every time I think about you ♪
♪ My heartbeat goes a-risin' ♪
- ♪ And I just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till I... ♪
♪ Till I die ♪
♪ There's nothing
That can beat like this ♪
♪ Faster as I close my eyes ♪
- ♪ Just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till the... ♪
♪ Till the night ♪
♪ Now as long as you are here by my side ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ I keep walking on ♪
♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪
- ♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
- ♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ I keep walking on ♪